We're in Soul trying supposedly the best
我们在首尔尝试所谓的最好吃的甜甜圈。让我们先从肉馅的那个开始。
donuts in Korea. Let's start with the
我打算留到最后吃那个，因为我不确定那个的味道。但是
meat one. I'm going to save till last
这个是巧克力焦糖酥脆口味的。
cuz I'm not sure about that one. But
非常、非常酥脆。这个是白巧克力柠檬口味的。
this one is like chocolate caramel
它确实非常柠檬味，但我尝不到任何白巧克力。我只尝到
crunch.
很多柠檬味。这个就叫作可可。那上面就写了这些。
Very, very crunchy. This one is the
一个普通的甜甜圈。我以为这个里面有什么特别的东西。黄油
white chocolate lemon.
和炼乳。
It's definitely very lemony, but I don't
我感觉心跳加速。到目前为止，那个是我最喜欢的。像这种黄油
taste any white chocolate. I just taste
非常细腻顺滑，很容易吞咽。通常我不太喜欢吃黄油块，
a lot of lemon. This one was just called
但这个出乎意料地好吃。是的，这个是开心果馅的。
cacao. That's all it said.
哇哦。
Just a normal doughnut. Thought there
哇哦。这个很清爽。
was something inside of this one. Butter
and condensed milk.
I like felt my heart heart start to
palpitate there. So far, that one was my
favorite. Like that butter is just so
cream and smooth and it just goes down
really easy. Usually I'm not a huge fan
of eating blocks of butter,
surprisingly, but yeah, this one's the
pistachio filled one.
Oh wow.
Oh wow. This one's like refreshing.
After all those like super like sweet
总的来说，超级甜的那种
ones, this one's really refreshing and
这一个真的很清爽
it's filled. Man, I don't know how I
而且很满足。哥们儿，我不知道我对这个感觉如何
feel about this. Pushcido and maple like
推迟多和枫糖浆，就像甜甜圈上的肉一样
meat on a donut. Dude, I'm not really
哥们儿，我并不喜欢那种类型的人
like that type of guy. Usually if I eat
通常如果我吃肉，我就直接吃肉
meat, I just like eating straight meat.
哦，那个。那是最贵的那个
Oh, that. That was the most
可能是因为推迟多
expensive one. Probably because of the
但我再也不想吃了
pushcido. But I don't ever want to eat
我再也不想再看到那个了
that again. And I don't ever want to see
等你韩国旅行的时候再尝尝吧
that again. Save it for your trip to
Korea.